(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T12:28:57.333965",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
OUR SPARKLE Ookami Mio 1st Live
[Ookami Mio 1st Live "Our Sparkle" - Sept 10, 2025]
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: Notice to Attendees]
Sponsor 協賛 みるハコ by JOYSOUND
[Sponsor: Miruhako by JOYSOUND]
おい！
Hey!
あ、こっちこっちこっち！
Ah, over here, over here!
今日、二人じゃないんすね
You're not just two today, huh?
え、二人？さっきの…
Huh? Two? The ones just now...
ここでやった人たち
The people who performed right here!
え？
Huh?
心で抱きしめる 今は少しだけ愛を信じられる
Holding you close in my heart, I can believe in love just a little bit now
ジョイしてこうぜ！JOYSOUND X1
Let's Joy! JOYSOUND X1
本日は大神ミオ ファーストライブ『Our Sparkle』にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming today to Ookami Mio's
1st Live, "Our Sparkle"!
うっち！うっち！うっちだよー！大神ミオだよーー！
Uchi! Uchi! It's me, Uchi! It's Ookami Mio!
わあ、みんな元気だー！
Wow, everyone's so energetic!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To help everyone enjoy the live to the fullest,
I have a few announcements to share.
はーーい！
Okay!
元気いいねー！
You've got great energy!
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Filming, recording, and the use of recording equipment
during the performance are strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell,
please notify a nearby staff member without pushing yourself.
はーーい！
Understood!
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Mosh pits, crowd surfing, jumping wildly, throwing objects
onto the stage, or disturbing others is strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいねー！
Please follow the rules and enjoy yourselves!
はーーい！
Okay!
守っていただけない場合は、ご退場いただく可能性もあるので、気をつけてねー！
If you cannot follow them, you may be asked
to leave, so please be careful!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Also, cameras for video streaming and photography
will be in the venue, and audience seats may be filmed.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
These videos and photos may be used for promotions,
so we appreciate your understanding in advance.
はーーい！
Understood!
みんな、いい子だねー！
You're all such good listeners!
あいも変わらず 上ばかり見ておかしくなる やる気萎っていく
Without changing, looking only up makes me strange, my motivation withers.
責任掛けっつけ 明日に背を向け 色褪せた過去とやり合ってんだ
Burdened with blame, turning my back on tomorrow, fighting a faded past.
抑えつけるほどかさを増していく劣等感 その他諸々
Inferiority complex and more growing the more I suppress it.
溺れる前に夜を染め上げなきゃ
I have to dye the night before I drown.
敵じゃないポーズ決め込んで 不満さんポッケ詰め込んで
Striking a pose like it's nothing, stuffing dissatisfaction in my pockets.
叩き割ってみれば増える ひとつまたひとつ
Smash them open and they multiply, one by one.
もう飲み込めないくらい
More than I can swallow anymore.
ほらくれてやるよ 食え全部 ちゃんと噛んで味わいながら
Here, I'll give it to you, eat it all, chewing and tasting it properly.
感想聞いてみてもいいですか
May I ask for your impressions?
僕ら灰を背負ったままナイトループだ そう壊れるまで
We carry our ashes in this night loop until it breaks down.
嘘をぎゅっとしたサイコルールじゃ もう縛れないよ
Bound by tight lies in a psycho-rule, I can't be tied anymore.
正解すら間違っているんだ そうだろう 誰も彼も馬鹿みたい
Even the right answers are wrong, right? Everyone's like a fool.
イタイの飛んでいけナイトループだ そう上がれるまで
Fly away the pain, it's a night loop, until we rise up.
やいのやいのどうしようもないから もう騙さないで
Complaining endlessly with no way out, don't fool me anymore.
あと少しで絶望と希望の境界線 背伸びすれば届きそうな称賛
Just a bit more to the border of despair and hope, praise almost within reach on tiptoe.
あいも変わらず 上ばかり見ておかしくなる やる気萎っていく
Without changing, looking only up makes me strange, my motivation withers.
責任掛けっつけ 明日に背を向け 色褪せた過去とやり合ってんだ
Burdened with blame, turning my back on tomorrow, fighting a faded past.
抑えつけるほどかさを増していく劣等感 その他諸々
Inferiority complex and more growing the more I suppress it.
溺れる前に夜を染め上げなきゃ
I have to dye the night before I drown.
敵じゃないポーズ決め込んで 不満さんポッケ詰め込んで
Striking a pose like it's nothing, stuffing dissatisfaction in my pockets.
叩き割ってみれば増える ひとつまたひとつ
Smash them open and they multiply, one by one.
もう飲み込めないくらい
More than I can swallow anymore.
ほらくれてやるよ 食え全部 ちゃんと噛んで味わいながら
Here, I'll give it to you, eat it all, chewing and tasting it properly.
感想聞いてみてもいいですか
May I ask for your impressions?
僕ら灰を背負ったままナイトループだ そう壊れるまで
We carry our ashes in this night loop until it breaks down.
嘘をぎゅっとしたサイコルールじゃ もう縛れないよ
Bound by tight lies in a psycho-rule, I can't be tied anymore.
正解すら間違っているんだ そうだろう 誰も彼も馬鹿みたい
Even the right answers are wrong, right? Everyone's like a fool.
イタイの飛んでいけナイトループだ そう上がれるまで
Fly away the pain, it's a night loop, until we rise up.
やいのやいのどうしようもないから もう騙さないで
Complaining endlessly with no way out, don't fool me anymore.
あと少しで絶望と希望の境界線 背伸びすれば届きそうな称賛
Just a bit more to the border of despair and hope, praise almost within reach on tiptoe.
あいも変わらず 上ばかり見ておかしくなる やる気萎っていく
Without changing, looking only up makes me strange, my motivation withers.
責任掛けっつけ 明日に背を向け 色褪せた過去とやり合ってんだ
Burdened with blame, turning my back on tomorrow, fighting a faded past.
抑えつけるほどかさを増していく劣等感 その他諸々
Inferiority complex and more growing the more I suppress it.
溺れる前に夜を染め上げなきゃ
I have to dye the night before I drown.
敵じゃないポーズ決め込んで 不満さんポッケ詰め込んで
Striking a pose like it's nothing, stuffing dissatisfaction in my pockets.
叩き割ってみれば増える ひとつまたひとつ
Smash them open and they multiply, one by one.
もう飲み込めないくらい
More than I can swallow anymore.
ほらくれてやるよ 食え全部 ちゃんと噛んで味わいながら
Here, I'll give it to you, eat it all, chewing and tasting it properly.
感想聞いてみてもいいですか
May I ask for your impressions?
僕ら灰を背負ったままナイトループだ そう壊れるまで
We carry our ashes in this night loop until it breaks down.
嘘をぎゅっとしたサイコルールじゃ もう縛れないよ
Bound by tight lies in a psycho-rule, I can't be tied anymore.
正解すら間違っているんだ そうだろう 誰も彼も馬鹿みたい
Even the right answers are wrong, right? Everyone's like a fool.
イタイの飛んでいけナイトループだ そう上がれるまで
Fly away the pain, it's a night loop, until we rise up.
やいのやいのどうしようもないから もう騙さないで
Complaining endlessly with no way out, don't fool me anymore.
あと少しで絶望と希望の境界線 背伸びすれば届きそうな称賛
Just a bit more to the border of despair and hope, praise almost within reach on tiptoe.
あいも変わらず 上ばかり見ておかしくなる やる気萎っていく
Without changing, looking only up makes me strange, my motivation withers.
責任掛けっつけ 明日に背を向け 色褪せた過去とやり合ってんだ
Burdened with blame, turning my back on tomorrow, fighting a faded past.
抑えつけるほどかさを増していく劣等感 その他諸々
Inferiority complex and more growing the more I suppress it.
溺れる前に夜を染め上げなきゃ
I have to dye the night before I drown.
敵じゃないポーズ決め込んで 不満さんポッケ詰め込んで
Striking a pose like it's nothing, stuffing dissatisfaction in my pockets.
叩き割ってみれば増える ひとつまたひとつ
Smash them open and they multiply, one by one.
もう飲み込めないくらい
More than I can swallow anymore.
ほらくれてやるよ 食え全部 ちゃんと噛んで味わいながら
Here, I'll give it to you, eat it all, chewing and tasting it properly.
感想聞いてみてもいいですか
May I ask for your impressions?
僕ら灰を背負ったままナイトループだ そう壊れるまで
We carry our ashes in this night loop until it breaks down.
嘘をぎゅっとしたサイコルールじゃ もう縛れないよ
Bound by tight lies in a psycho-rule, I can't be tied anymore.
正解すら間違っているんだ そうだろう 誰も彼も馬鹿みたい
Even the right answers are wrong, right? Everyone's like a fool.
イタイの飛んでいけナイトループだ そう上がれるまで
Fly away the pain, it's a night loop, until we rise up.
やいのやいのどうしようもないから もう騙さないで
Complaining endlessly with no way out, don't fool me anymore.
あと少しで絶望と希望の境界線 背伸びすれば届きそうな称賛
Just a bit more to the border of despair and hope, praise almost within reach on tiptoe.
あいも変わらず 上ばかり見ておかしくなる やる気萎っていく
Without changing, looking only up makes me strange, my motivation withers.
責任掛けっつけ 明日に背を向け 色褪せた過去とやり合ってんだ
Burdened with blame, turning my back on tomorrow, fighting a faded past.
抑えつけるほどかさを増していく劣等感 その他諸々
Inferiority complex and more growing the more I suppress it.
溺れる前に夜を染め上げなきゃ
I have to dye the night before I drown.
敵じゃないポーズ決め込んで 不満さんポッケ詰め込んで
Striking a pose like it's nothing, stuffing dissatisfaction in my pockets.
叩き割ってみれば増える ひとつまたひとつ
Smash them open and they multiply, one by one.
もう飲み込めないくらい
More than I can swallow anymore.
ほらくれてやるよ 食え全部 ちゃんと噛んで味わいながら
Here, I'll give it to you, eat it all, chewing and tasting it properly.
感想聞いてみてもいいですか
May I ask for your impressions?
僕ら灰を背負ったままナイトループだ そう壊れるまで
We carry our ashes in this night loop until it breaks down.
嘘をぎゅっとしたサイコルールじゃ もう縛れないよ
Bound by tight lies in a psycho-rule, I can't be tied anymore.
正解すら間違っているんだ そうだろう 誰も彼も馬鹿みたい
Even the right answers are wrong, right? Everyone's like a fool.
イタイの飛んでいけナイトループだ そう上がれるまで
Fly away the pain, it's a night loop, until we rise up.
やいのやいのどうしようもないから もう騙さないで
Complaining endlessly with no way out, don't fool me anymore.
あと少しで絶望と希望の境界線 背伸びすれば届きそうな称賛
Just a bit more to the border of despair and hope, praise almost within reach on tiptoe.
泣かないと決めたあの日から
Since the day I decided not to cry,
本当はずっと苦しかった
It's actually been painful all along.
叫んでも変わらない世界に
In a world that doesn't change no matter how I scream,
爪を立て 牙を剥け 炎を灯せ
Grow claws, bare your fangs, and light the flames!
「どうしようもない」
"There's nothing I can do,"
呟いて誤魔化したかった 羨望 理想像
I muttered, wishing to mask my envy and ideals.
「くだらない」
"How pointless,"
吐き捨てて手前横切った 激情走馬灯
I spat out as a flash of intense passion crossed my mind.
誰かが決めた正解と幸せ
The "correct answers" and happiness someone else decided,
“自分らしさ”に縛られて
Bound by "being yourself,"
比べた分遠のく夢 これが生き様か？
A dream that drifts further away the more I compare—is this how I live?
ignite my soul
抗う野生 戦うことをやめちゃいけない
Rebel wildlife, you mustn't stop fighting!
(I'm a survivor , I'm a fighter)
(I'm a survivor, I'm a fighter)
紛れもない僕にしか僕を救うこと出来ないから
Because no one else but undeniable me can save myself.
(I'm a survivor , I'm a fighter)
(I'm a survivor, I'm a fighter)
いま、黎明
Now, at dawn.
「あれがほしい」 簡単には言葉に出来たらいいのに 逃げ癖
"I want that"—if only I could easily put it into words, my habit of running away.
「かわりたい」 変わらないのは世界じゃなくて僕なんだ 気付いたんだ
"I want to change"—I realized that what doesn't change isn't the world, but me.
与えられた安全圏 熟す道化
A given safety zone, a ripening clown.
型破り アウトローの勝利
Unconventional, an outlaw's victory.
正攻法じゃ もうカンスト ここが正念場か
With a straightforward approach, it's already maxed out—is this the crucial moment?
ignite my soul
穿つ 野生 見据えた 先 に 煙る 光
Piercing wildlife, the smoke-veiled light ahead.
(I'm a survivor , I'm a fighter)
(I'm a survivor, I'm a fighter)
誰でもない僕だけは僕を信じて貫きたいから
Because I want to believe in and push through with only myself, no one else.
(I'm a survivor , I'm a fighter)
(I'm a survivor, I'm a fighter)
何処からか声がするのさ
A voice is coming from somewhere.
傷付きながらでも辿り着いた激動
The turbulence I reached even while getting hurt,
叫ぶ本能 戦うことをやめちゃいけない
Screaming instinct, you mustn't stop fighting!
(I'm a survivor , I'm a fighter)
(I'm a survivor, I'm a fighter)
ほら、鮮明
Look, vividly clear.
泣かないと決めたあの日から
Since the day I decided not to cry,
叫ぶように溢れ出した渇望
The yearning that overflowed as if screaming,
在るがまま剥き出しの心で
With a heart bared just as it is,
爪を立て 牙を剥け 炎を灯せ
Grow claws, bare your fangs, and light the flames!
ignite my soul
滾る 野生 戦うことは生きることだ
Surging wildlife, fighting is living!
(I'm a survivor , I'm a fighter)
(I'm a survivor, I'm a fighter)
紛れもない僕にしか僕を救うこと出来ないから
Because no one else but undeniable me can save myself.
(I'm a survivor , I'm a fighter)
(I'm a survivor, I'm a fighter)
何処からか声がするのさ
A voice is coming from somewhere.
傷だらけの僕が生き抜いた勲章
The medal won by my scarred self surviving through,
叫ぶ本能 戦うことは生きることだ
Screaming instinct, fighting is living!
(I'm a survivor , I'm a fighter)
(I'm a survivor, I'm a fighter)
さあ、黎明
Now, at dawn.
ネオンライトは眩く
Neon lights are dazzling,
街灯明滅 通り過ぎ
streetlights flickering as I pass by.
窓の向こう 夜の風に
Through the window, in the night wind,
空を見た
I looked up at the sky.
忙しい足取り 私だけが
A busy pace, as if only I
取り残されたようで
was left behind,
また光に揺られる
swaying in the light once more.
心の中で私を消して
Erasing myself within my heart.
追いかけた過去 背中合わせの
The chased past and back-to-back
希望 密度 押しつぶされぬように
hope and density, so as not to be crushed—
だから君と ここにいる時間は
That's why the time I spend here with you
言葉にできず 見つめ合うだけ
cannot be put into words, just gazing at each other.
思考回路 ぼやけたままで さあ
My thought circuits remaining blurred, now...
光を掴むまで
until I grasp the light.
何処まで往こうか
How far shall I go?
ネイビーな夜空に映る
Reflected in the navy night sky,
過去の自分
my past self—
夢見がちだった
I was too prone to dreaming.
見たくないモノ
The things I didn't want to see
照らすハイビームに
illuminated by the high beams,
走る焦燥感
a surging sense of impatience.
跳ね除けて前へ往けば
Shaking it off and pushing forward,
信号は全色を無くし消えた
the traffic lights lost all colors and vanished.
確かめたい この道が繋ぐ場所を
I want to make sure where this road leads.
深く、深く紺になる
Deeply, deeply turning dark navy,
夜を往ける この加速度
this acceleration traveling through the night—
光さえ超えてゆける程に
going fast enough to surpass even light.
強く、強く踏み込んで
Stepping down firmly and strongly,
僕は駈ける ただ真っ直ぐに
I run straight ahead,
譲れない想いを抱いて
holding onto unyielding feelings.
標識だらけの街を抜け出して
Slipping out of the sign-filled town,
未来を探していた
I was searching for the future.
常識も何も 全部雑踏と化していた
Common sense and everything else had turned into mere hustle and bustle.
何処まで往けるのなんて聞き飽いた台詞吐いて
Uttering the tired line, "How far can you go?"
曇った窓ガラスに書いた本音 すぐに指で消した
I wrote my true feelings on the foggy windowpane and quickly erased them with my finger.
懦者でも揺るぎない軌跡
Even as a coward, an unwavering trajectory,
確かな願いを胸に 遥か遠くへ
holding a certain wish close to my heart, far into the distance.
錆び付くように躓いても
Even if I stumble as if rusting,
この真っ暗闇を 燈し進む
I light up and press through this pitch darkness,
ただ一つ 答えを追いかけて
chasing after just one answer.
脆くても良い この腕で
Even if fragile, with these arms
掴む為に手を伸ばすよ
I reach out to grasp it,
打ち鳴らす鼓動の限り
to the limit of my beating heart.
何度 この道で迷って
How many times have I lost my way on this road,
見失って どこへ往くの
lost sight, and wondered where I'm going?
目指す場所も その意味も 一つしかないのに
Even though there is only one destination and one meaning.
曇った視界は 夜に溶けて もう一度
My cloudy vision dissolves into the night once more,
視線の先 僕を連れて往くよ きっと
surely leading me ahead of my gaze.
深く、深く紺になる
Deeply, deeply turning dark navy,
息を吸って 今 加速を
taking a breath, now accelerating—
傷付く程に強くなると
growing stronger the more I get hurt,
確かな色動き出す
a true color begins to stir.
纏ってゆけ その身体で
Wrap yourself in it, with that body,
鮮やかな夜空の果てへ
to the edge of the vibrant night sky,
忘れないように
so as not to forget.
深く、深く 紺になれ 今を生きる
Deeply, deeply turn navy, living in the present,
この加速の 光さえ超えてゆける 場所へ
to a place where I can surpass even the light of this acceleration.
強く、強く 踏み込んで 僕は駆ける
Stepping down firmly and strongly, I run
ただ真っ直ぐに 譲れない想いを抱いて
straight ahead, holding unyielding feelings.
まだまだ走るよ みんなついてきて
We're still running! Everyone, follow me!
どこまでいこうか マイビイビーな夜空に
How far shall we go into the baby-navy night sky?
映る昨日の自分 夢見がちだった
My past self reflected there was so dreamy.
ベイビーフェイスに さあ よなら
Now, goodbye to that baby face.
見たくないもの 照らすハイビームに
The high beams illuminate what I don't want to see,
走る衝動を 飛び抜けて前へ ゆけば
and as I break past the surging impulse and move forward,
信号を皆色を無くし消えた
the traffic lights lost all their colors and vanished.
確かめたい この道が繋ぐ場所を
I want to make sure where this road leads.
何度 この道で 迷って
How many times have I lost my way on this road,
見失って どこへ往くの
lost sight, and wondered where I'm going?
目指す場所も その意味も 一つしかないのに
Even though there is only one destination and one meaning.
曇った視界は 夜に溶けて もう一度
My cloudy vision dissolves into the night once more,
視線の先 僕を連れて往くよ きっと
surely leading me ahead of my gaze.
みんな生きろよ
Everyone, live on!
深く深く紺になる 息を吸って 今加速を
Deeply, deeply turning navy, taking a breath, now accelerating—
傷付く程に 強くなると 確かな色 動き出す
growing stronger the more I get hurt, a true color begins to stir.
纏ってゆけ その身体で 鮮やかな夜空の果てへ
Wrap yourself in it, with that body, to the edge of the vibrant night sky.
忘れないように
So as not to forget.
深く、深く 紺になれ 今を生きる
Deeply, deeply turn navy, living in the present,
この加速の 光さえ超えてゆける 場所へ
to a place where I can surpass even the light of this acceleration.
強く、強く 踏み込んで 僕は駆ける
Stepping down firmly and strongly, I run
ただ真っ直ぐに 譲れない想いを抱いて
straight ahead, holding unyielding feelings.
確かな色 動き出す 纏ってゆけ
A true color begins to stir, wrap yourself in it,
その身体で 鮮やかな夜空の果てへ 忘れないように
with that body, to the edge of the vibrant night sky, so as not to forget.
深く深く紺になる 今を生きる
Deeply, deeply turning navy, living in the present,
この加速の 光さえ超えてゆける 場所へ
to a place where I can surpass even the light of this acceleration.
強く、強く 踏み込んで 僕は駆ける
Stepping down firmly and strongly, I run
ただ真っ直ぐに 譲れない想いを抱いて
straight ahead, holding unyielding feelings.
重い思いを抱いて、
Leaving the heavy memories behind,
止まらないで、
don't stop,
走り続ける君を知るから。
knowing the days keep running on.
きっと未来は色にあふれ、
Surely the future is overflowing with colors,
まだ見ぬ世界をカラフルに染める。
dyeing the unknown world in vibrant hues.
もっと自由になりたいからずっとずっとずっと夢見ているの。
Because I want to be more free, I've been dreaming on and on.
空に光る星のように、
Like a star shining in the sky,
輝きたいと願う夜。
I wish to glow and light up the night.
広い世界に存在を証明したくて、
I wanted to prove my existence in this wide world,
できない言葉数数えても、
even if I count countless words I cannot say,
胸が苦しくなるだけでしょ。
it only makes my chest ache more.
私だって絶対あの日の夢のようになれるはず。
I should have been able to reach that dream day,
響く鳴音の中ほら、道なる景色、遠く感じてたのに、
though I felt the scenery echoing within the ringing melody,
近づけた気がしてたんだ。
it just slipped through my fingertips.
外伸ばしたこの手の先、描きたい理想が、
Beyond that outstretched hand and horizon,
想像を越えて、きっと見つける私との色、ずっとずっとずっと追いかけるの。
I've finally found my own color, chasing it on and on.
限りあることおまえだった、
Even if it seemed bound by limits,
瞳に映るすべて、
it reflected in everyone's eyes,
変わりゆく世界のリズム通って、
flowing to the rhythm of a changing world.
とちっくめなくてもいいの、
Even if things don't go as planned,
不安感感じても、私だけの色で描こう。
I want to paint it with my own unique color.
きっと未来は色にあふれ、まだ見ぬ世界をカラフルに染める。
Surely the future is overflowing with colors, dyeing the unknown world in vibrant hues.
もっと自由に羽ばたくから、ずっとあの日のままに。
Because I want to be more free, I've been dreaming on and on.
そっと伸ばしたこの手の先、描きたい理想が、
Beyond that outstretched hand and horizon,
想像を超えて、やっと見つけた私の色、ずっとずっとずっと描いていくの。
I've finally found my own color, painting it on and on.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
というわけで、まずは自己紹介からしたいと思うんですけど、
Well then, first I'd like to do a self-introduction, but...
「おかみみお」だよって言ってもらったらうちの自己紹介が完成するので、
if you all say "Oogami Mio," my introduction is complete.
言ってもらってもいいですか？
May I ask you to say it?
おうちおうち、おうちだよー！
Oogami Mio!
本日はおかみみおのソロライブ開催おめでとうございます！
Today is Oogami Mio's solo live! Congratulations!
うちはおめでとうって言われる側だと思うんだけど、たぶん。
I think you're all saying "Mio, congratulations," right?
ソロライブの衣装どうかな？
Is this outfit for the solo live cute?
かわいい！嬉しい！
Cute? I'm so happy!
なんと、なんと今回、あの、6年と、まあもうちょっとで7年活動してきて、しっぽが解放されてるんです！見て見て！
Look, look! My tail has finally been unsealed!
ここ の 足 に ね 、 あの 巻きつい て い た
My tail wrapped around my leg just now...
尻尾 が ね 、 見え ちゃっ た 感じ な ん です けれど も
You could kind of see it, huh?
（笑）
(giggles)
嬉しい の 、 なんか 。
But I'm kind of happy about it.
まあ 、 これ は うち の 自信 の 表れ と 言い ます か 。
Well, you could say this is a sign of my confidence.
自信 が つい た から こう やっ て 尻尾 が 解放 でき た と いう こと で 。
Because I've gained confidence, I was able to let my tail free like this!
この 舞台 に 押し上げ て くれ た みんな 、 ありがとう ！
Everyone, thank you for lifting me up onto this stage!
はあ …… 。
Whew...
ちょっと 汗 かい てき ちゃっ た かも 。
I might have worked up a bit of a sweat.
（笑） ありがとう ござい ます ！
(laughs) Thank you so much!
いやあ 、 ちょっと ね 、 最初 だ し コール アンド レスポンス と か し て み たい けど 。
Man, since it's the very beginning, I wanted to try doing some call-and-response, but...
どう か なあ 。
I wonder how it'll go.
じゃあ 、 やっ て み ちゃおう か な 。
Well, why don't we give it a try?
まあ 、 さっき ね 、 あの 狼 みお に は なっ て もらっ た から 。
Well, earlier I had you all become wolf mios, so...
うーん 、 どう しよっ か な 。
Hmm, what should we do?
じゃあ 、 ええ と 、 「 狼 みお 、 ソロ ライブ 」っ て 言っ たら 、 みんな 「 あわー ！ スパークル ー ！ 」って 大きい 声 で 言っ て もらっ て も いい です か ？
So, um, if I say "Ookami Mio Solo Live," can everyone shout out "Awaaa! Sparkle!" really loudly?
ありがとう ！
Thank you!
じゃあ いき ます よ 。
Alright, here we go.
狼 みお 、 ソロ ライブ ！
Ookami Mio Solo Live!
すっごい よく 聞こえる 。 おめでとう ！
It sounds amazing! Congratulations!
はあ 、 ちょっと ね 、 配信 で 見 て いる 。
Whew, also to everyone watching the stream...
そこ の 君 も 、 ツリー 好き の みんな も よく 見え てる よ ！ コメント ありがとう ね ！
You over there, and everyone loving the stream, I can see you clearly! Thank you for the comments!
いっぱい うち の ね 、 可愛い 姿 を スクショ し て もらえ たら 嬉しい なんて 思い ます 。
I'd be so happy if you could take lots of screenshots of my cute moments!
（笑） 現地 の みんな は 一旦 記憶 に キャプチャ し て ね 。
(laughs) Everyone here live, make sure to capture it in your memories!
（笑） ありがとう ！
(laughs) Thank you!
はい 、 え 、 そして 、 え 、 シャープ みお スパークル で 、 え 、 スクショ や 感想 の ポスト も よろしく おお願いします ！
Right, and please post your screenshots and impressions with the hashtag #MioSparkle!
いやあ さあ 、 もう 狼みお ソロ ライブ 始まっ ちゃっ たら もう あっという間 に 終わっ ちゃう の か と 思う と 、 もう MC も まだまだ 終わり たく ない ん だ けど 。
Man, knowing that once Ookami Mio's solo live starts, it'll be over in a flash—I don't want the MC to end just yet!
もう 始まった 瞬間 から 終わる 心配 し てる ん だ けど 。
I've been worrying about it ending the moment it started!
はい 、 今日 は ね 、 たくさん 最高 に キラキラ な 思い出 作っ てこ う ね ！
So today, let's make lots of sparkling, wonderful memories together!
はい 、 そして 、 え 、 チラ見 せ 枠 の 皆 さん に は 残念 な おしらせ な ん です けれど も 。
Right, and for those watching the sneak-peek preview, I have some unfortunate news...
ああ …… まあ 、 あの 、 現地 の 皆 さん は ね 、 最後 まで 見れる の は 確定 な ん です が 。
Ah... well, everyone here live is guaranteed to see the very end, but...
無料 配信 は ここ で お 別れ と なり ます ！
The free stream will end right here!
はい 、 と いう わけ で ね 、 あの チラ見 枠 の チケット を 、 え 、 買っ て いただけれ ば 続き が 見れ ます の で ぜひ ぜひ 買っ て いただけれ ば なっ て 見ーフ の 皆 さん も 思っ てる よ ね 。
Right, so if you buy a ticket for the sneak peek, you can watch the rest, so I hope you'll consider purchasing one!
思って ます ！
We really do!
よろしく お願い し ます ！ ナイス 。
Please look forward to it! Nice.
今 の 、 あれ なん か 、 みお が すな よ 。 どう だ よ 。
That right now... it sounded like Mio was sulking. How was that?
なんか 、 い 、 今 、 今 なり みお ファー の 声 が 聞こえ て くる よう な 。
It sounded like I could hear "Imanari Mio-fa" voices.
騒がしい 。
So noisy!
みお ファー の 声 で いい す ね 。
That's classic Mio-fa for you.
はい 。
Yeah.
と いう わけ で 、 そろそろ 次 の 曲 行き ます か ！
Alright, with that said, shall we move on to the next song?!
狼 みお ソロ ライブ 、 盛り上がっ て いく ぞ ！
Let's get even more hyped up for Ookami Mio's Solo Live!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.